Take me home
I will warm up
your bed
Meow!
I name you...
Xiaohei!
You already decided?
I'm "little white", he's "little black".
Sweet, huh?
It's rather random...
So you named me also rather randomly?
On a second thought...
"Luo Xiaohei". This name does have profundity.
He woke up.
Hi!
Now you scared him.
Xiaohei!
Don't be afraid.
Come here!
Sorry.
Mom! Where's the plate?
I don't know, it wasn't me...
I know, Xiaohei must have pulled it in there.
I don't think so... Will you check it?
I hope nothing's wrong...
He's come out.
Why for?
I wonder why he's so obedient now...
You did scare him back there.
He's got a blue tongue.
Do cats have blue tongues?
How should I know?
All right.
Tomorrow I'll have to buy cat litter and tray.
What are those for?
That'll be the cat's toilet.
Can't he use ours?
Show me a cat that would sit on it.
Well...
I'm sure you're not just an ordinary cat.
Where'd you come from, after all?
You're so nice.
Your owner must have loved you.
They must have had no choice but to leave you.
From now on, I'll be your owner.
I'm Luo Xiaobai.
Nice to meet you, Xiaohei!
Xiao...
Xiaohei?
In fact...
I am a prince who has been cursed.
Thank you for lifting the curse off me.
By kissing you?
Yes.
So clichéd...
Would you like to come to my castle tonight?
I must properly thank you.
I can't go.
Gotta go to school tomorrow.
Let us meet at the weekend, then.
Okay...
Diting! The Sky Pearl was stolen.
Do you admit your sin?
Yes, master.
I will definitely recover the Sky Pearl.
Easier said than done,
for vast is the sea of beings.
I have hit the demon and made him revert to his original form.
He should still be nearby.
Very well. Don't return without the Pearl.
Understood.
Xiaohei!
Good kitty! Come here!
You're gonna be late! Come quick!
Run!
Okay!
I'm the
father
Mom, Xiaohei started to eat your breakfast.
Looks like he won't eat cat food.
Lucky my first thing today was to buy some.
This way we can share our food with him.
Shouldn't you be going?
Oh no! Gotta go to school!
Wait for me, please!
Thank you...
A cat?
I'm home!
What?
Xiaohei tried to run away?
Yeah, he somehow opened the door.
I caught him and brought him back.
You should decide if we let him go or not.
Sure...
Xiaohei!
Xiaohei, where are you?
Where did you go?
Xiaohei!
Do you want to leave?
I know, this place is full of cars and dogs...
If you really want to leave,
I'll take you out of town this weekend.
Okay?
Xiaobai!
What are you doing up there? Come down!
Sure!
Coming!
Hello? Hi, Shan Xin!
Yeah, sure.
Hey!
You wanna see Xiaohei?
Okay, when can you come over?
At the door?!
'Sup.
Hi!
Long time no see, Xiaohuang!
This is for Xiaohei.
Thanks!
I'm sure he'll love it.
Hello, Shan Xin.
Hello, Mrs. Luo.
I'll be cleaning here, you just go play.
Okay.
I forgot your mom always looks like that.
'Sup, nihao.
Go say hello to him.
What's wrong, Huang?
Seems like he's scared of him.
Cats tend to be quite timid.
He's not so interested.
Watch and learn.
You see now?
Catch it!
He caught it!
One more time!
Xiaohei, you're awesome!
Not at all.
The point is to do your best not to catch it.
See?
Come!
Is he making fun of me?
Girls! I'm leaving for work!
Okay!
Of course you found an excuse again.
I did bring Xiaohuang to meet Xiaohei.
So I end up having to take care of him.
Please!
Whose side are you on this time?
The Horde!
You got up, lazy cat?
Xiaohei, what happened to your tail?!
What are those?
Your tail!
So a cat's tail can turn into tiny kitties!
Hei-shu!
"Heishu"?
I see, your name's Heishu!
Xiaohuang!
Come down, Xiaohuang!
Be a good kitty!
Come down!
Xiaohuang!
Xiaohei!
Xiaohei, bring him back!
Hello?
Mom?
Yeah, I'm at Xiaobai's.
What? You come over?
Nothing. I'll wait for you.
Huzzah, fair maiden!
Do you want a silver scale breastplate?
Silver scale breastplate!
First class product!
Only 5 golds--
What happened?
No idea.
Xiaohuang...
He's on heat.
You two can't procreate.
From this day on,
I'll be your faithful servant.
You only have to sign this contract, my dear!
insurance
Who was that?
A minor character.
Did you finish packing? Don't forget anything!
I know.
Have you called over?
Yes.
Who picked it up?
Cousin Gen.
Your school stuff?
They're dead!
Got enough socks?
I'll wear sandals.
Your toothbrush?
I forgot that!
Fly!
Mine.
Come quick, they're gonna fight!
Don't cry.
You can play with it.
Xiaohei!
Maybe he's on the roof.
You're right! I'll check!
But no climbing up!
Xiaohei!
Heishu?
I can't find him anywhere...
Don't worry, he must be playing hide-and-seek.
But what if we won't see him anymore?
It's gonna be alright.
Xiaohei!
Where've you been?
Isn't that my dress?
How did you make it so dirty?
Bad kitty!
Found you.
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me